# Andrei Bolshakov



a.bolshakovy@gmail.com



linkedin.com/in/bolshakovandrei



https://t.me/Bolshakov\_Andrey

### **Summary**

Solution-focused developer coming from financial service background with a passion for team projects and client satisfaction. I am keen on development for being creative and solving complex challenges.. Whatever I do, I try to figure out the logic of what is happening, identify structure and patterns, understand ways of processes optimisation.

My vast experience with a variety of teams and subordinates allows me to easily adapt to a newly-introduced fast-paced environment, to quickly learn new things and to efficiently interact with colleagues and customers to strengthen the teamwork and bring our vision to reality.

### **Experience**



#### **Software Developer**

Freelance

Sep 2022 - Present (10 months)

Latest freelance project - advanced telegram bot for "GoodChemistry" shop

## Back-end Developer

Yandex.Practicum.Studio

Jan 2022 - Sep 2022 (9 months)

Project for the festival of young playwrights "Lubimovka"

Developed the backend part of the project. Created an API.

As part of the team, successfully brought the project to release.

## 

Yandex Practicum

Nov 2021 - Sep 2022 (11 months)

Training on the course Web development.

Practically implemented more than 5 projects, some of them:

- \* Social network "The Place" (React.js)
- \* Project "Learning to learn" (JavaScript, HTML, CSS)
- \* Website "Movies Explorer". (MERN)
- \* Single-page website "Travels in Russia" (JavaScript, HTML, CSS)

## Head of Sales

Kapital Life, Rosgostrakh, Reneissans insurance, Sogaz,

Jan 2009 - Sep 2022 (13 years 9 months)

Automated sales management processes. Participated in the work of the technology committee.

Ensured achievement of the company's strategic sales and profitability goals.

# ☐ Junior Back End Developer

#### Yandex Practicum

May 2020 - Feb 2021 (10 months)

Training on the course Python Bak-end Development.

Practically implemented 7 projects, some of them:

- \* Social network of bloggers "YaTube" (Django, PostgreSQL, CI/CD, Yandex Cloud Deployment)
- \* Website "Media Content Review Database". (Python3, Django, PostgreSQL, Docker, CI/CD)
- \* Service "Product Assistant". (Python3, Django Rest Framework, Django, CI/CD, Docker, PostgreSQL, Git, Yandex Cloud Deployment)

## C# Developer

#### Freelance

Jan 2010 - Dec 2020 (11 years)

Development of trading algorithms, according to the original methodology for the creation of infrastructure alogrithmic trading on international financial markets.

#### **Education**

### Yandex Practicum

Web Delveloper, Web Development Nov 2021 - Sep 2022

#### Yandex Practicum

Back-end Developer, Python Development May 2020 - Feb 2021

## RANEPA

Master of Business Administration - MBA, Business Administration and Management, General 2007 - 2009

# 

Bachelor's degree, Business/Managerial Economics Feb 1994 - Jun 1998

## Omsk Automobile and Armored Engineering Institute

Bachelor's degree, Electrical and Electronics Engineering Aug 1990 - Jan 1994

#### **Skills**

Python (Programming Language) • Django • REST APIs • PostgreSQL • MongoDB • Linux • HTML5 • Cascading Style Sheets (CSS) • React.js • JavaScript